Oopsie.
Decaf double tall
nonfat capp for Bruce.
You got it, buddy.
That's a wonderful choice,
Bruce.
- Thank you, Sam. Take care.
- It certainly is.
One Caramel Macchiato.
It's very hot.
Good morning.
Vanilla grande no-foam latte.
That's a wonderful choice.
- Thanks, Sam.
- Yeah.
Hey, Sam. They called.
It's time for you to go.
Oh, yeah, it's time.
It's time, buddy.
It's time for me to go now.
It's time for me to go now,
George!
Good luck.
It's time.
It's time now.
Hurry up. The first floor
is two more floors.
Hurry up.
The second floor...
one more floor.
I have to go to Room 324
on the third floor.
Rebecca!
You the one responsible
for this?
I'm sorry.
Too late for sorries.
Get over here and hold her hand.
Are you OK?
Got a live one, Gert.
Good. Come on.
Focus and breathe.
This is it.
And it's a girl!
It's OK.
What's her name?
Lucy in the sky with diamonds.
Lucy Diamond Dawson.
You're my daughter.
I'm your father.
Get them to make the bus stay.
They're leaving.
- I'll get them.
- They're leaving.
Excuse me.
Hang on one second, please.
Becca!
Becca! The bus is going!
Uh-oh.
Didn't you just go to sleep?
Let me see.
OK.
Lucy, you look beautiful
this morning.
You look very beautiful.
Look at that, Lucy. Nose.
OK. Yeah, l...
Oopsie.
What the hell are you
doing to that baby?
What's the matter
with the baby, Sam?
Everything
is just so tiny, tiny.
Will you come over here
and help me?
You know I can't do that.
What does her mother say?
Her mother said,
"This isn't my life...
"and I didn't want
a baby with you.
"I just needed
a place to sleep."
What if the baby's sick?
Bring her over here.
Sam, babies need food
every two hours.
Sorry.
I'm sorry, Lucy in the sky.
You know...
critics and fools said that
that song...
had some mysterious meaning,
but John always said...
it came from a picture
his son Julian drew...
of his friend Lucy O'Connell.
So I made a good choice?
You made
an excellent choice, Sam.
Now, what time does
this little diamond wake up?
What time does
She wakes up all the time.
Let's just assume
she wakes up at 6:00.
Keep your TV on Nickelodeon.
I want you to feed her first...
when "Hogan's Heroes"
comes on.
And then again.
Wait until "I Dream of Jeannie."
And then, feed her
when "I Love Lucy" comes on.
We have to be quiet.
I've seen nothing.
I know nothing!
Such a nice man for an officer.
What are you doing?
I'm just getting Lucy asleep...
and you're making noise
and everything.
- Oh, sorry.
- We're here for video night.
Eight years every Thursday
video night, and you forgot?
I'm sorry.
It's always every first Thursday
of every month...
video night at Sam's house.
And I forgot.
Yeah, and I forgot.
Becca's gone.
"Gone with the Wind."
1939,
directed by Victor Fleming.
That was a very sad movie.
Here we go.
Everything changes now.
Soon you'll forget about
Wednesday night at IHOP...
and then Friday night
at karaoke...
and I got hit by a car today.
You did?
It was probably that guy
from the V.A.
Did you bring
"Kramer vs. Kramer"?
I see what's happening here.
I see.
So this is all my fault now.
Don't tell me you forgot again.
I broke a date with
a daydream to come here.
It's your mother.
Hi, Robert. Hello, boys.
It's me, Estelle.
Ma, I told you.
Video night's over at 9:00.
It's only 6:30.
Well, I guess
I'll just wait downstairs.
Sure there isn't anything
I can get you?
No, Ma. You can wait downstairs.
That's fine.
OK. See you later, Rob.
Bye, Estelle.
What a pretty baby.
Hi, little baby.
- Doesn't she look smart?
- She does.
She looks smart.
That baby looks so darn smart.
It's amazing how smart she is.
She's very smart.
She really does.
I think she's really beautiful.
Of course she looks smart.
She's already reading the paper.
Double Macchiato,
low fat, low foam.
That's a wonderful choice.
Oh, my God!
An ice cube went down...
Thank you. Oh, my God.
Can I get another drink, please?
Iced cappuccino.
That's a wonderful choice.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Annie, I can't take her
to work anymore...
because she's too big now.
- Annie.
- That was her first word.
- See?
People worry you're not smart.
Papa.
Yes. Oh, you smell so good.
You can tell a lot about people
by the way they smell.
Daddy, why does the snow flake?
Because snow...
because snow flakes.
Daddy, what is mustard made of?
Because it's yellow ketchup.
Daddy, why are men bald?
Sometimes they're bald
because their head is shiny...
and they don't have hair on it.
So their head
is just more of their face.
Daddy,
are ladybugs only girls...
or are there boys, too?
And if there are,
what are they called?
Yeah, the Beatles.
Daddy, where does the sky end?
Why does the moon
follow me home?
Why is the sun orange?
Where does the hour go
in Daylight Savings?
Daddy, do I look more
like you or Mommy?
Daddy...
Do you think
she'll ever come back?
Paul McCartney lost
his mother when he was little.
And John Lennon lost his mother
when he was little.
Annie says that sometimes
God picks the special people.
That's what Annie says.
Daddy, did God mean for you
to be like this...
or was it an accident?
What do you mean?
I mean you're different.
But what do you mean?
You're not like other daddies.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
It's OK, Daddy.
Don't be sorry. I'm lucky.
Nobody else's daddy
ever comes to the park.
Yeah, we are lucky.
Aren't we lucky?
Rooty Tooty Fresh and Fruity.
Sunnyside up, not too runny.
Two sausage links.
French pancakes
instead of buttermilk.
Fruit topping on the side.
The Funny Face special.
I think it's funny when
you say "Funny Face special."
French, not buttermilk.
Fruit topping on the side.
Not on top.
You're getting a funny face.
That's a wonderful choice.
Thank you, Grace.
Thank you
very, very, very, very much.
You got it, Sam.
Is that too big?
I think that's a little too big.
You need a pair of
good, sturdy school shoes.
These are sturdy.
The arches
are very important.
No. Sturdy is boring, Sam.
These shoes light up, OK?
These are really good shoes
for school.
I know. I love them.
I found the most perfect shoes.
They look like the shoes
that Dorothy wore...
played by Judy Garland
in "The Wizard of Oz"...
1939,
directed by Victor Fleming.
These are pink.
These are also Velcro.
They might have
a little arch in there, too.
Sam, these are
probably too big...
but I thought maybe
Lucy would like those.
When we were at the zoo,
she liked the animal prints.
But these are for adults.
But when we went...
I don't know you.
I don't know who you are.
I like these, Daddy.
She knows what she likes.
That's why she likes these.
- Black goes with everything.
- How much are these?
$16.19 with tax.
Because I have $6.25.
That's all you have?
I didn't get my whole check
because I had to go...
to the parent and teacher
meeting this week.
I'm sorry. It's $16.19.
I couldn't go to work
all day that day.
It's OK, Sam, because
I have $3.00 to contribute.
Sam, I've only got
two plus two...
but I need one for stamps,
so 1... 2... 3.
Joe's got $1.50.
Yeah. So, is that enough?
If there's a God.
I'll count it.
Do we get a balloon with these?
All of us, or just her?
"And I will eat them
here and there.
"I will eat them anywhere."
"I do so like
green eggs and ham.
"Thank you, thank you,
Sam I am."
One more time?
- Yeah.
- OK.
"Green Eggs and Ham"
by Dr. Seuss.
"I will eat them with a mouse.
"And I will eat them
here and there.
"Say, I will
eat them anywhere.
"I do so like
green eggs and ham.
"Thank you, thank you,
Sam I am."
One more time?
Daddy, it's my first day
of school tomorrow.
I don't want to be too sleepy.
Everybody says Bob's Big Boy
has the best hamburgers.
Can we go there Wednesday
instead of IHOP?
But Wednesday is IHOP.
Just one time?
Yeah, but Wednesday is IHOP.
Can I read just the beginning?
Just the beginning.
"Green Eggs and Ham"
by Dr. Seuss.
There are four stages
of a butterfly's life.
The first three stages are
from egg to larva to cocoon.
Last...
They're hard to remember
because there's so many stages.
It's hard to remember.
33 days. It lasts 33 days.
Spiders and insects
are members of the ants...
ants... anthro...
Conner. Anthropod class.
Anthropod class.
However, spiders and insects
are very different.
- Spiders have six legs...
- Eight legs.
Eight legs and two body parts,
and they're called...
Conner. What are you doing?
You know this stuff.
- No, I don't.
- You do know it.
You wrote that part,
remember?
I wanted to do potato bugs
anyway. Oh, forget it.
I think he can make
that boy feel better.
Sorry, Mr. Egg.
What's wrong with your father?
Why's he acts like a retard?
He is.
- Are you?
- No.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
How do you know?
He told me.
He's a retard.
Well, it takes one to know one.
It's wonderful to have you
for company tonight.
Isn't it wonderful to have
Conner for company, Lucy?
Yeah. "Sorry, Mr. Egg."
"They per..."
"They perched in...
"Si...
silen..."
Silence.
Yeah. Silence.
"They perched in silence
for a long time."
Your teacher gave you
a really hard book this time.
That's really
a hard book to read.
"How can we be so..."
Differ...
Different.
Oh, yeah. OK.
"How can we be so different
and feel so much alike?"
I don't like that book.
Let's read
"Green Eggs and Ham."
Yeah! OK.
"Green Eggs and Ham"
by Dr. Seuss.
"I am Sam."
Hey, you.
Hey, handsome.
"Premature baby
claims he's Cupid.
"Has arrow to prove it."
You believe that?
But if he has the arrow,
that's the only thing.
You got a good point.
This is the International
House of Pancakes quiz.
And Lucy found the word "beet."
I want to surprise her
and find the word "carrot"...
but it's hiding.
Carrot!
- Where?
- C-a-r-r... carrot.
Carrot. It's right there.
And you're smart.
You would be a good mother.
Do you tell good stories?
- I got stories up the wazoo.
- Really?
You come with me and relax...
and I'll tell you
some nice stories.
Lily, what did I tell you
about selling on my beat?
Put it down on the table.
It's the International
House of Pancakes quiz.
Put your hands behind your head.
What did l...
Do you have any weapons on you?
He touched me
on my private place.
At such a time as this,
Annie's the boss.
First time in 19 years
I actually believe a guy...
when he says he didn't know
she was a hooker.
You say that like
it's a good thing.
Did you brush your teeth?
They don't sound
like they were brushed.
She forgot to brush her teeth.
Let him go.
Says he never spent
the night away from his kid.
Trouble. Oh, boy,
I'm really in trouble.
Are you in trouble, too?
Yeah, I'm in trouble, too.
It gives us great insight
into what she must be feeling.
Mr. Dawson,
it's becoming clear...
that she's holding herself
back in the classroom.
It's as if she's literally
afraid to learn.
No one doubts
that you love your daughter.
But the Department
of Child and Family Services...
contacted us.
They shared with us
that your records show...
that your
intellectual capacity...
is around that of a 7-year-old.
Our concern is what happens
when Lucy turns 8.
Mr. Dawson,
do you understand...
what Ms. Wright is trying
to tell you about Lucy?
John wanted to try new things.
And it wasn't Yoko's fault.
No, it wasn't Yoko's fault.
Annie says you can hear it
on The White Album.
Because John wanted
to try new things.
"They perched in silence.
How can we be so diff..."
Diff... diff...
I don't know that word.
Yes, you do. That's the word
that starts with a "D."
I'm tired.
I don't believe you.
Are you calling me a liar?
Yes. I think
you have to read the word.
No.
Yeah, you have to read
that word.
No.
Yeah. Here it is.
There's the picture
where they're all perched.
- Now read the word.
- No!
I won't read the word!
I'm your father...
and I'm telling you
to read the word.
I can tell you to
because I'm your father.
I'm stupid.
- You are not stupid.
- Yes, I am.
You are not stupid,
because you can read that word.
I don't want to read it
if you can't.
No, because it makes me happy.
It makes me happy
hearing you read.
Yeah. It makes me happy
when you're reading.
"They perched in silence
for a long time.
'How can we be so different...
and feel so much alike? '
Mused Flitter.
'How can we feel
so different...
and be so much alike? '
Wondered Pip.
'I think
this is quite a mystery."'
Keep going.
They have Oreo
ice cream mud pie.
This is so great.
Yeah, this is so great.
And the menu says...
you can have your
favorite breakfast all day.
That's so great, too, you know.
Because you wanted
to come to a new place...
so we came
to a different place.
Hey, guys.
Can I get you coffee?
No, I don't drink coffee.
OK. What can I get you guys?
I'd like the Super Big Boy
with a root beer float, please.
OK. What about you?
I would like to have
two eggs, sunnyside up.
But not runny, OK?
Not runny.
And then I would like
to have French pancakes...
with the fruit topping
on the side.
We don't have French pancakes.
We have French toast.
No, I don't want French toast.
I want French pancakes,
like at IHOP.
Just the same kind
like they have at IHOP.
That's what my favorite
breakfast is, OK?
They're those thin pancakes.
The crepe pancakes?
I don't even want crepes.
I want to have
French pancakes...
with the fruit topping
on the side.
That's what
I want to have, please.
Thank you.
We don't have that, though, sir.
Do you want
regular pancakes and jam...
I don't want something else!
Why did you ask me that?
I'll see.
Maybe they have something...
- Yeah, ask Bob!
- OK.
Ask Bob's Big Boy.
Because the customer's
always right.
I understand that...
The customer's always right.
Because when Lucy comes
through the door...
everybody says, "surprise!"
You gotta stop bouncing
for a second.
You'll say, "surprise!"
Can we keep bouncing?
You'll have to come down.
After Lucy gets here
and we say, "surprise."
So you have to assume
surprise position.
Should we rehearse it
one more time?
Assume the surprise position.
Annie was supposed to warn us.
Brad, hit the light.
Surprise!
It's not her.
Hi. I don't know
if you remember me.
I'm Margaret Calgrove...
Department of
Child and Family Services.
We met at the police station.
Put the present there.
You have to hurry,
because Lucy's coming.
Come on, hide with us.
Come on, over here.
Annie said Lucy's coming up
the stairs right now.
So you have to assume
the surprise position.
I bet she already knows.
Why are you being
a party pooper?
She's coming now.
You have to assume
the surprise position.
Don't touch me.
I've got cooties!
It's contagious!
Hey, what are you doing?
Get your hands off him.
What are you doing
touching my kid?
- Surprise!
- Leave him alone!
Happy birthday.
Daddy?
You don't
have to call him Daddy.
She said you're not
her real father anyway.
She said she was adopted.
Lucy!
Given the fact
that the father...
was arrested
for solicitation...
couldn't control
his emotions...
endangering other children.
No, you can't!
It's her birthday!
Ms. Calgrove also cites...
Mr. Dawson's mental delays
which raise serious questions...
about his ability
to properly parent.
Run!
I find at this time...
it's not in the best interest of
the child to remain in the home.
And I order her detained...
until a formal
jurisdictional hearing.
Mr. Dawson.
Is there anything
you'd like to add?
I wanted to make it
a really special surprise party.
So I went, and I got plates
at the Pic 'n' Save...
in yellow and in pink...
like a princess.
And then I went
to the toy store...
and I got balloons
with the helium in them.
- Mr. Dawson?
- Yeah.
It sounds like you gave her
such a lovely party.
Yes, I'm sure it was.
Right now, I want to talk to you
about your legal rights.
OK. There's room
at this table...
if anybody wants
to sit next to me.
I just want to talk to you
about your legal rights...
so if you have not already
retained legal counsel...
the court will appoint
someone for you...
to present your case
on January 5. OK?
That's a month from now...
so I come back here
in one month with Lucy.
No, Mr. Dawson. You will have
monitored visits...
two times a week
for two hours.
And now we're moving on
to 4-D, Parker...
What do you mean?
You will see Lucy
two times a week for two hours.
Why isn't Lucy
going home with me?
I want her to go home with me.
Not today.
Thank you, Mr. Dawson.
4-D. Parker vs. Van Wert.
Thank you.
Of course the judge
picked the lawyer.
For God's sake,
put it together.
She's the one who took
Lucy away from you...
so it's time that
you get your own lawyer now.
You guys think I'm guilty?
- No, Sam.
- You didn't kill anybody.
I miss Lucy, Sam.
Me, too.
You need
a personal injury lawyer...
because you have been
personally injured.
When Dustin Hoffman
was trying to keep Billy...
from going back
to Meryl Streep...
his lawyer told him that
it would cost him $15,000...
and that's if we win.
- $15,000!
- And that's if we win.
Don't worry about money, Sam.
Get the best. Century City.
Here. Look at that.
Let me show you
what it looks like.
Rothman, Glenn,
Harrison, and Williams.
This is one of the best ads
I've seen in the Yellow Pages.
So maybe we're going to win.
- We're gonna win.
- One of the best ads I've seen.
With Rothman and Glenn
and Harrison and Williams...
we're gonna win.
Did Fred Kimble call?
I'm already 20 minutes late.
What did Michelle Kresge say?
Was she defensive?
That's ridiculous.
What happened with my car?
Because it wasn't my fault.
Oh, I know.
This is Mr. Dawson.
There was some confusion
with the temp last week...
How do you do? I'm Sam.
Mr. Dawson. It's a pleasure.
Since somebody made a mistake...
unfortunately
we only have a little time.
Hold my calls
unless it's my kid.
I'll have a grande 2% capp.
That's a wonderful choice.
Can we get you something
to drink?
Is it for free?
- My treat.
- OK. Thank you.
Yeah, I would like
a glass of milk.
Did you get that, Patricia?
Yes.
And Lucy
had an ice cream cake...
with pink flowers...
not white...
and she likes
cherry vanilla because...
If that's Jake Hiller,
put him through.
Jake, no.
So I got cherry...
- Your son's on line two.
- Did you get that?
Tell him to hold
for just one second.
I have to go. The what?
...melted together as orange.
No. Have a nice weekend.
And Brad wanted
a princess on top...
with little pink shoes.
I think there's a...
I think your son's on line two.
Oh, my God. Willy?
Patricia, get Willy back.
Well, keep trying.
Mr. Dawson, quite bluntly,
you can't afford to hire me.
Yeah, because I make
$8.00 an hour at Starbucks.
Per hour. It's an hourly rate.
I could pay you per hour.
Mr. Dawson, I'm sorry,
but I have...
I have to be in court in
eight minutes with the Kresges.
But good luck to you.
Don't give up.
I'm not giving up.
Where am I going?
I can show you out.
Patricia, where are my keys?
This is her
on her first birthday.
December 6.
That's her birthday.
And this is Lucy two years old.
This is Lucy seven years old
on her birthday...
the day they took her away.
Your son's on line two.
Willy, hi.
Jackson told Wyatt he wasn't
my best friend anymore.
Could we possibly talk
about this when I get home?
Willy? Come on, you're
not gonna talk to me now?
I bought a bag of your favorite
lemonade jellybeans.
God!
I hate that stupid coffee table.
How many times, Patricia,
have I told you...
to get rid of
that crappy coffee table?
It's OK.
You have a son, Rita Rothman
Glenn Harrison Williams.
If they took him
away from you...
would you do what
Robert said and got...
the fastest-talking,
four-name lawyer you could?
I may know someone who handles
these kinds of cases.
I'll see if she can help you.
Leave your number with Patricia.
Your therapist
is on line one.
Tell him you can't find me.
I'm gonna leave my number
with you, OK?
I'm ready to make coffee.
Decaf nonfat latte.
It's coffee up to here,
nonfat milk up to here...
and chocolate
or cinnamon sprinkles.
That's pretty good, Sam.
I'll think about it.
We'll come up with a promotion
that's good for you.
But I know what that means.
When I worked as a janitor
at the La Reina Theater...
I asked Mr. Jenkins
if I could be a ticket-taker...
and he said
he would think about it.
And Jimmy Peters got the job.
And he let his friends
in for free.
I promise you, Sam.
We'll come up
with something for you.
You have my word.
Word, words, words.
I need more than that.
I need to make coffee.
I need to pay my lawyer.
I am celebrating
congratulations to us.
These are the moments.
Good night.
Grande, 2% capp.
I brought that for you.
By any chance,
did you call your friend?
The one
that does this kind of work?
I don't have her number anymore.
We lost touch.
Yeah, that happens.
If you get
back in touch with her...
and you find her number,
will you call me?
I'm just in the middle of...
It's a special...
Yeah, I'll call you.
OK. Yeah.
Is that the new janitor?
Oh, it's a...
a case I'm helping out with...
sort of a pro bono thing.
What's that supposed to mean?
Cracker went down
the wrong pipe.
You think I don't do pro bono?
Have another glass, please.
On me.
No, on you. It's pro bono.
I do pro bono.
I know. You go, girl.
You just spread that love.
Spread it all around.
Stop. Driver, stop the bus.
Stop the bus.
Wait for me. I got it.
Lucy, he's an hour
and 45 minutes late.
You'll only have
a few minutes left.
You can leave if you want.
- Lucy!
- Daddy?
I'm here. I'm here.
It's Daddy. I told you!
Oh, shoot!
I spilled it all. Hi.
And guess her name is.
Her name is Rita Harrison.
Lovely Rita Meter Maid?
Yeah, and Harrison like George.
Is she going to help us?
She can't help us...
but if she ever finds
her friend's number...
who does this kind of cases,
she's gonna call me.
You've grown.
Have I?
Yeah. Because your ears
are bigger...
and your eyes are older.
Guess what I'm gonna get
when I get my next paycheck?
I'm gonna get
an answering machine...
because then you can call
and leave a message.
You can say,
"Hi. This is Lucy."
We can't afford
an answering machine.
Yeah, because
I'm gonna get a big promotion...
a promotion that's big.
They'll let you make coffee?
Always set
your dreams high, Lucy.
I'm sorry, Daddy.
It was all my fault.
Don't say that.
It was not all your fault,
so don't say that.
I wouldn't want
any daddy but you.
Did you hear that?
I said I was sorry!
I said I didn't want
any daddy but him.
Why don't you write that down?
Let me make sure
that I'm clear here.
Are you telling me
neither of you...
wants custody of your child?
He has created a monster.
He is exactly like him.
Here we go again.
It's the same old story.
The tears and the tears.
Oh, my God.
Are you really...
You cannot stand emotion.
I'm right here with you.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Hi! Did you get in touch
with your friend?
Because I need legal advice now.
You said
I couldn't afford you...
so I have to talk to somebody.
That's why I told you
I would be your lawyer pro bono.
I don't understand
exactly what you mean.
You told me
that you would be my lawyer?
Sam, I'm your...
Golly, because
I must have misunderstood.
I told you that
when we first met.
You said
you would be my lawyer?
Yes. Sam...
You're my lawyer!
That's right. I'm your lawyer.
And I can pay you per hour.
- No, no, no.
- On the hour.
Pro bono. It's free.
My lawyer for free.
Now, you... God.
Thank you.
Because I have to get this.
It's "Urgent, open immediately"
For my lawyer for free!
They want to have you
evaluated by a shrink...
and your appointment is today!
At 3:00.
It's today! It's now.
I don't actually
want to go to a shrink.
Sam, you don't actually
have a choice.
It's court-ordered.
The lady in your office
is crying.
Patricia,
I'm in the middle of a meeting.
Can you get him out of here?
Don't feel bad.
Sam, come with me.
We'll get through this.
Will you excuse us?
It's their turn now, not yours.
Theirs.
If you leave now,
you can make this...
and you have to make it.
But I have to take
the number 13...
downtown Wilshire express
to Grand Street...
then I transfer to the number 34
at Cesar Chavez Avenue...
because that used
to be Brooklyn Avenue...
and my grandfather
had a bakery on it...
when it was Brooklyn Avenue.
I don't think I can get there
at the time I'm supposed to.
Go, for Christ sakes!
Green means "Go."
I don't like to go to shrinks.
You and me both.
Right or left?
Which is it gonna be,
bonehead?
Right turn ahead.
Right on Vermont?
That'll be another 20 minutes,
you idiot!
Did your mommy make you
go to a shrink, too?
No. Well, sort of.
I spent the whole time
talking about her.
Well, that's nice.
- Office.
- Dialing home.
Office! God damn it!
You're going much faster
than everybody else.
I wonder if you noticed that,
because I noticed that.
Go!
No more shrinks.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Dawson...
but if I were you, I wouldn't
waste any more of my time.
Sorry, Mrs. Dawson, but I think
you should put Sam in a home.
Sam in a home.
Mr. Dawson,
you do understand...
that since I'm a
court-appointed psychologist...
the traditional client-therapist
confidentiality...
will be waived.
Do you understand that?
That the confidentiality
will be waived.
Good. Let's begin.
I went to a doctor one time
who had an orange office.
All the walls
were painted orange.
Do you know her?
She has an orange office...
and she's in Van Nuys.
I wanted to ask you about Lucy.
How old is she now?
She's six. She's seven.
She just had a birthday,
I think.
How was that party?
"Before you read
your message...
"press the red button
for record."
Let's start with the O.G.M.
What? I don't know.
I don't think it's working.
I think it's because
it's a used machine.
It's not used. It's pre-owned.
A guy bought it
for his auto shop...
and then he got a secretary.
Testing, 1, 2, 3.
That's a good code.
I can remember that... 1, 2, 3.
4, 5, 6.
7, 8, 9.
9, 10, 11, 12.
Quick. You're recording.
Hi. This is...
Hi. This is Sam.
I'm not home.
No, you really
don't want to say that...
because you don't want
to tell them you're not home.
- Then I'm lying.
- Everybody's lying.
Sam, you are on the air.
Hi. How are you?
Maybe you sound
a little bit too excited.
And maybe you might think
about lowering your voice...
so maybe Lucy can hear you.
Go, Sam.
Hi, Lucy.
Thank you for calling me.
That was good.
But did I sound like
a good father?
But it's an outgoing message...
so I think you need to sound
a little more outgoing.
Hi. This is Sam.
I'm not ho... Shoot.
Hi. This is Sam!
I think you should
sound like a normal person.
From the heart.
This is... Hello.
Thank you for calling.
This is Sam.
Wow.
I feel that was a very touching
moment right there.
I felt that one.
High-five.
We have a lot to go over,
and I have five minutes.
Rothman, Glenn,
Harrison, Williams...
is on the 29th floor.
That's 29 floors up...
and the elevators
are actually over there.
Keep up.
Got to do my cardio. 120.
Got to get to 125
to make it count.
I need that list of names
from you...
people who can testify
that you're a good father...
despite your handicap.
Just my husband.
I didn't mean your handicap.
I meant your disability.
The fact that you're retarded...
that's not the right word.
I don't know what to call you.
Sam. You can call me Sam.
All right! Hello. Hi, Todd.
I was out of range.
How you doing?
What do you mean,
what's that supposed to mean?
You're supposed
to be taking him to karate.
Are you eating?
No, I will not hold on.
Go pick him up.
I can't hear you.
I'm in the car.
They put you through to me.
I'm losing you.
What makes Sam a good father?
The important thing is for
Sam to be a very good father...
is to be there for her...
because the smarter Lucy is,
the smarter she will get.
So what makes Sam a good father?
Lucy's first word was "Annie..."
and her fifth word was "Joe."
And I'm Joe.
Sam is a very good father...
because he likes green things...
like I like green things
very much.
I like green peas.
My cousin Luke works for
the organization...
environmental organization
Greenpeace...
and they like
to save the whales.
I like whales.
"Moby Dick" was one of my
all-time favorite classics...
by Herman Melville.
Wait.
Why are you recording this?
It's often necessary...
You didn't say anything
about a tape recorder.
- Who's listening?
- Me.
What is that supposed to mean?
Nothing.
Who are you really?
I need to speak
to my lawyer now.
I don't think you realize
what you're up against.
We have to be in court
in three days...
and we don't have
a decent witness.
Now, you've got to know
someone who can testify...
who's been to college...
or has a degree of some kind...
or has some way
of expressing themselves...
that will make the court
believe you deserve...
to get your daughter back.
I need coffee. Big, tall.
Tall is the smallest.
Yeah, of course.
Once you think of this person...
and there has to be one person,
call me at work.
Because
I'm going back there now...
to my seven other cases. What?
Mrs. Robeck. I'm on the 405.
The traffic is horrible.
You want this
for here or to go?
Dorothy?
Oh, no. No.
Tow truck is towing your car.
Son of a bitch.
It's towing your car.
No, wait! Stop!
It's my car. Stop.
But, Annie, it's just one day.
And Lucy needs you
because you went to college...
and you can
give the right answers.
And we can't lose her.
I'd make it worse for you.
I can't do it.
Don't you think I would
if I could?
All rise for the Honorable
Judge Phillip McNeilly.
Hi, guys.
Hi, Sam.
Boy, you did a wonderful job
making those signs.
You're welcome, Sam.
Good luck, buddy.
Go get 'em.
Although,
at her birthday party...
I believe her true feelings
about her father were revealed.
Objection.
"True feelings revealed"?
Your Honor,
Ms. Davis is an expert...
appointed by the court
for her opinion.
I'll allow it.
Then every child who rages...
because they
didn't get to stay up...
that extra hour to watch TV...
Any child who said
they hated their parents...
because
they didn't want a bath...
would be a prime candidate
for foster care?
- Objection, Your Honor.
- Sustained.
I think they want you to stop.
Really?
Thank you, Sam.
Yeah, OK.
Brad's wearing a tie today...
and I think the tie
looks wonderful on you, Brad.
You look great, too.
There's a lady...
she's writing everything down.
Watch what you say.
I have the best friends
in the whole world.
Continue with your witness,
Mr. Turner.
Ms. Davis, I assume
in your therapy session...
that Mr. Dawson extolled
his parenting ability.
On the contrary.
Mr. Dawson admitted
he felt very confused at times.
Actually,
that he felt terrified...
that he'd made and would
continue to make...
and I can quote here...
"Huge mistakes,
huge mistakes...
"mistakes that are huge."
Thank you.
No further questions.
You're a mother,
aren't you, Ms. Davis?
Yes, I am.
Would it be fair to say that...
as a parent, you've been
confused from time to time...
possibly overwhelmed
on occasion...
even though
you're a wonderful mother?
If Ms. Davis
has never had a moment...
where she's been confused
as a mother...
it would bias
her expert opinion.
I know that I have
many moments as a parent...
where I felt
I've made huge mistakes.
Objection.
Get to the relevant point,
Ms. Harrison.
The point is, you've never
had those moments...
have you, Ms. Davis?
Moments that every parent
I've ever spoken to has.
Moments where the task is
so unbelievably challenging...
that you feel retarded...
disabled in some way.
Moments where everyone seems
to have the key but you.
Really, to be honest...
Yes or no?
Please answer the question.
I didn't really
feel right now...
Let me rephrase the question.
- When your son O.D.'d...
- Objection.
If Ms. Davis didn't feel
she had made mistakes...
mistakes that were huge...
it might bias her opinion
toward Mr. Dawson.
I'll allow it.
Ms. Davis,
when your son O.D.'d...
did you feel that you
might have made mistakes...
mistakes that were huge?
Yes.
No further questions.
You made her cry.
I got lucky.
Oh, no.
That's not nice to make her cry.
Only in there.
And your secretary
when you hated your desk.
Green and yellow
on the same plate.
Could you separate
the lima beans...
from the corn, please?
Sam, don't be impossible.
Can I have
the spinach omelette...
only egg whites,
no fat, no oil, no butter.
- And extra mushrooms?
- Absolutely.
My treat.
- No, no, no...
- My treat.
My pro bono.
That means she doesn't
have to pay. I pay.
Sam, do you really
want to get this...
or are you just trying to...
trying to act like a...
What do you mean?
You know, like... Never mind.
I'm a grownup.
I didn't say that.
You think what they think.
You're my lawyer,
and you think what they think?
I don't have a chance.
I think...
you deserve a fair trial.
Do you think what they think?
Sam can't order food
or Sam can't pay a check.
Sam can't take care of Lucy?
It doesn't matter what I think.
It matters that we win.
It matters what you think.
It doesn't matter to them
what I think.
It matters to me!
$14.33.
That's five ones...
Two quarters. 14.33.
Five ones and two quarters.