www.titlovi.com
And no wonder,
for Satan himself
masquerades as an
angel of light.
Where's the first-aid kit?
David!
Coming, Mom!
Whisper
Hey, Sid.
Welcome back to the new world
Come on, check this out.
Hey, you know what? Um, Max.
Look. I've got to be honest with you
You wanna buy this place?
I won't even rob of this place
Yeah, it's gonna be all mine
Ours
Look just because you work in the kitchen inside
doesn't mean that's the only option around here, OK?
No, Sidney. Max is a businessman,
We've been working on menus.
And you know what? I
've got a business plan.
And it ain't got nothing to do with
paper hats and napkins and menus
I've done with all that shit, Sid.
Hey, look. I 've got this sweet dig
this December with this guy named Jones
We grab one little rich kid,
big pay day, everybody wins
Don't listen to him. OK?
You know what? It's a nice idea.
But think about it, Max. You've got no
money. No collab. No banks gonna touch you.
I'm gonna do this, Sid.
Well, I'm sure you will.
I'll call you in a couple
of weeks, OK? I mean it.
Get out of here.
It says here you've
worked food service before.
I've sure ordered in Quincy,
Walten. A few places in Newport
And with 50,000 dollars loan, you think you
resurrect the old Hazel Street Diner, huh?
It's a corner shop, two busy streets,
a lot of foots and all the traffic.
Yes, Mr Truemont. I've reviewed that. It's
not nothing. Not really something either.
How it go?
Did you get it?
You know, Sid called.
I'm gonna take that job, Rox.
I have no place else to go.
OK, sweetheart. I've got
to set up for your party.
So Chloe can take over from here.
But I like it better when you do it.
Sandborn's party?
Abrakazzam!
Weren't that great, guys?
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Now, hey. Don't you guys try
this at home with your pets now.
Are you ready?
Let see if you can make them vanish.
1..
Santa!
Ho! Ho! Ho! One for everybody!
One for everybody!
- OK. OK.
Careful. Alright.
Over here.
No fighting.
OK. OK. OK. OK
Abrakazzam!
What you want for Christmas, David?
What do you want, Santa?
OK, birthday cake time.
Chloe, do you know where David is?
No, I'm not sure.
David!
Oh God
Kidnapped your son
Don't call the police
or we will kill him
I missed you, Sidney
I don't mind the new hair cut
You still glad you came along?
What are you doing
here anyway? Yoko? Hunu?
I'm good with kids, Vince
I got two? What do you want?
Err.. two
What the hell is that?
I must missed one.
No shit
Don't matter. Here's our boy.
Alright
I hope he took the right one.
Sidney
Take it easy
Stop it
Is everything OK, guys?
Yeah. Just run out of gas.
It's OK. It's OK.
We've got 'em covered.
Bobby, where the hell are
you? I've got two flats in 128
Bobby. For Christ's sake, I'm
talking to you, you lazy ass.
Help me
What if he sees?
Probably not
Not here
Max, get the van. Let's go.
Fine
But.. but, he would
have seen anything.
Do you want me to get you up?
You will never get up
Ms. Sandborn. I am Detective Witley.
Do you think you can find him?
Ma'am, as I said on the phone
we are pursuing all leads
In fact the matter is, the
kidnapper will probably call.
They usually do.
Ms. Sanborne. Detective Miles.
Look, I know this is a difficult time,
but I need the list of your employees..
Miles, can I talk
with you for a minute?
Excuse me
I got this covered. Alright? So you just watch,
take some notes and see how we do this up here.
OK, kiddo?
I thought this is the summer camp.
And how did you get
your hand on this place?
They've already gave me a
couple of bucks to watch it one.
Watch it one and collapse.
We all have better days.
Come on, let's get him inside...
It's not getting warmer around here.
It's frickin' freezing
Alright... I just
gonna put this on you
and get you inside where
it's warm. OK, buddy?
Alright. It's nothing.
It's just the wind, buddy.
Get out of here!
What? It's just a dog.
God blessed the 5th amendment
Nothing to be scared of
It'll be OK. I promise, alright?
I have to go to the bathroom
You've got your very
own bathroom just inside
Inside where? Where am I?
Don't worry about that, David.
Just work with us. Cooperate.
Hell, I don't know.
Think of this as game.
Are they going to hurt me?
No. Relax, buddy.
I'll give you an ice-cream
later. Would you like that?
Alright
In you go
You can take off your
blindfold now, David
Oh, you are a regular dent mother!
Vince
Sidney. if you let me know, I could
have brought my things and then..
we've could have more channels
then you know what to do then
I know I don't have to warn you, but
don't get too in touch with that kid. OK?
I got this
I'll put this up next.
- OK, thanks.
Oh, wi wi poo poo. What
is this foreign shit?
We are near the border, Vince.
Border of what? África?
Hey, there we go.
Hey, all we need now is pizza. We've
get ourselves one hell of the evening
Hey!
Damn, Mother. You see any phone book?
Put it dowm... It sure find a way
to lead the people to us around
Oh, hi mum. I'm in camp. I'm
gonna have fun for a few days.
It's gonna be fine. I won't let
anything happen to him, you know that?
I wish this will be over.
It'll be soon.
Bed time.
I found you this. I
thought you might get cold.
Why are you wearing that?
Well, it's so you won't see who I am.
You try to get some sleep, OK?
Looks uncomfortable. I won't
peek if you want to take it off.
OK, but it has to be our secret.
OK... I promise.
Late night I'll be at oasis
send your camels to bed
Do you love me, Max?
Maybe.
We'll have the money, and we'll
remove that if you hate it so much.
It can't be remove. The
scar I can bear but fear.
Baby, do you think we're bad people?
There is no commend
getting in kidnapping
It's stealing though
It's not stealing. Borrowing.
The kid's mother pays Jones.
David will back home tomorrow night
Who is this Jones anyway?
Doesn't matter. Sidney
also don't know Jones.
We'll get our half for
snatching the kid from home.
They did the exchange
when it is pay off.
Yeah, everybody wins.
Everybody wins.
Max
What is it, baby?
Nothing. I'm sorry I had a bad dream.
It's OK.
I'm hearing voices.
Will you check on David?
Yup
- Thanks
I don't like it here.
Shit
I'd put you on bed.
I'm not try to scare ya.
Why was my window open, Max?
Don't let the others hear you
calling me that, you understand?
Sorry. Sometimes you heard
things you don't want to.
Come on. It's alright. Go to bed.
Argh! Goddammit. The lil'
bastard busted my insulin.
Hey, hey. Calm down.
He.. he was in the trunk. He
must've kicked it or something.
He didn't do it on purpose.
Just relax, man. How
long do you need more?
Every morning, man. Right
now. Alright. Give me the keys
There must a pharmacy
around here somewhere.
There is one down the road but they're
gonna know you. Wait, we can't have that.
Well, I'll go to
Portsmith.! Give me the keys!
No, no. The cut is too close I have to
be at Welsham by 5 to talk with Jones.
I told ya that one car
thing was a bad idea.
The only bad idea is
bringing you along.
Hey! You take it easy.
Max, take him to Portsmith.
Got your prescriptions?
- Yes.
Everything you need?
- Yes!
Alright. Go. Get him
the hell out of here.
Oh no!
Come here, you little bastard!
Just leave him alone!
Knock it off!
He'd seen our faces
Let me just think a minute, alright?
Max, did you lock the door after
you looked at him last night?
What did she just say?
What did you do? What, did you
just tuck him in or something?
I swear I locked it.
You better than that. You know
what these means, don't you?
He probably knows our names too.
That freak kid will screw up again.
He'd seen our faces.
I don't know whether we
should let him go now.
What?
Just stop doing
anything till I get back.
Max. - Fine -
Hello! Diabetic!
Just a little bit more. Right
there. Good. Stay right there.
Alright. You hungry?
We gotta get back.
Man, Sidney never believe we got
Portsmith back that quick. Come on.
Just let kill few hours around
here just to cover ourselves.
Alright.
You have sown the wind and shall
reap a whirlwind, Hosea 87
Yes?
You're not helping
yourself around here, kid.
Am I in trouble?
I don't know. That
all depends on you.
You think you can aa.. forget about what
we look like? Our faces, voices, names?
Why?
How about I give you
a lil' bedtime story?
Couple years back, me and partner
doing job on this registry.
Everything has gone real smooth like untill
the teller tripped and sound the alarm
We warned her. Don't touch it. Don't
go near it. But she did it anyway.
Now, my partner. Well, he was
forced to blow her brain out.
Put the bullet right through her
head. Bang. Well, there you have it.
Nobody like a squealer.
Nice. What is it?
The teller's beads necklace. It broke
and it beads spilled all over the floor.
How do you know that?
I know a lot of things.
And I know it wasn't your
partner that killed the teller.
That was not what
you told the police.
You've told this story so many
times until you actually believe it
And I know something else.
What's that? What do you know?
I know that you're about
to have a heart attack.
Trying to scare me?
Too bad the car's not here.
Stop.
That was your plan, right? One
car means few complications.
I'm afraid you're
gonna die here, Sidney.
In this lonely little cabin and sit
around grovel in the living room.
Sidney
911. What's your emergency?
I'm sorry. Wrong number.
I'm sorry, Sidney.
Max will be here soon.
No. We can't let
them know we are here.
Hang on, OK? Max will be here soon
We'll be OK, then.
Max, baby. It's Sidney.
His heart. I'm so sorry, Max
David was keeping me company.
I was afraid to be alone, Max.
Sorry about Mr. Braverman.
Really, really sorry.
There's a lot of spiders. I
thought they hibernated in winter.
I wonder where the hive is?
The ground too frozen to bury him in.
We'll leave him here a couple of
days. Take him with us when we go.
Bigger share now.
The kid just bring bad luck.
So what are we gonna do?
We got two choices. We drop the kid
by the highway and call in the bust.
Wait, wait. Now, this is all for nothing and
we go back to be in broke? No, Goddamn way!
Or I go to that ring.
Try to find Jones.
I'm sure if this still
on, we'll get paid.
Yes, and it's bigger share now.
Vince, I swear God,
you and anyone else.
Sidney's share goes to his niece.
Alright. Whatever.
So, you're going to speak with Jones?
Wait. I thought we were
voting. I voted we let David go.
I've got a bad feeling
about this whole thing.
Max?
Take this. For protection.
From what? Elves?
Little boy abducted
Scion of Beacon Hill family
grabbed from own 8th birthday
Where is Sidney?
He died. He's dead.
He had heart attack.
That's so unfortunate.
Does the child still alive?
Of course
I took the picture.
His mother wants prove.
What the? I'll take another one.
Don't bother. You prepared
to call the mother, right?
Yeah, tonight.
You have what you need?
Yeah. Untraceable phone
scrambler. Expert dug it all up.
The guy's a pro.
Then, meet me at Boston
Park Avenue noon tomorrow.
You give the details off and your
money vanish. And watch your back.
So these are all the images of the marks
- Uh huh
Excuse me.
Ah, detective. It's
nice of you to join us.
The kid must be on a sippy time.
So, can we narrow
down the car or more?
Not really. But I seriously
look for a big American car.
What about the van?
Wiped clean before they torched it. But I
can be bit more thorough when we tow it in.
So we got nothing.
Not necessarily. Look. At least
two these things are the prints.
Including a clean
thumb and four fingers.
Chances are somebody got the record.
Ah, that's good. It's real good.
Come to take a ride, OK?
Where are we going?
Just got a few more things to
do, before we can get you home.
But I'm having fun here.
Not sure I wanna go home just yet.
What do you mean,
buddy? Of course, you do.
Come on. Let's go
Baby, we should turn back.
Too late for that.
Keep him down.
Sorry, sweetie.
You can look now, David
Alright. Scrambler,
ready. Decoder, we're on.
They might not be able to trace us.
I'm calling your mom, David.
Oh, good.
We're on. Don't tap
up the whole wire.
OK
Yes?
Ms. Sandborn?
Speaking.
We have your boy.
I want proves he's alive.
Yeah, alright.
OK.
David?
David, it's that you?
Come on, buddy. You're almost there.
Get him say something.
Say something.
Just say hello.
Come on, David. Don't be scared.
Yes, be scared.
You'll be very scared when you know
who I am and what I'm gonna do..
It's OK. You just say hello, honey.
Go ahead.
- Goddammit, say something.
Alright!
- Vince, don't hurt him!
Hey, what are you doing?!
Back off!
Vince, stop it! David,
it's OK. It's OK.
She.. she just said my name!
What's happening?
Damn it! You just told my name!
- Back off!
Why did you do that for?!
- Leave the kid!
Take it off, Max!
What are you doing?!
We lost them.
OK, let's get things
double next time.
Did you get the match?
No.
Any signal trace data?
- No
I'm sorry you had to hear..
Is David alive?
We didn't get the voice match.
Didn't have the location.
Is he dead?
Did they kill him?!
Catherine, we don't
know. We have no idea.
So, what you guys wanna do now?
Like really go for that ice-cream?
Alright, that's it!
- Vince!
Don't you hurt him!
It's OK. It's OK. Everything's fine.
It's not OK!
What are you doing, Max?
I should have done
it a long time ago!
Stop using my damn name. It's
good for a kid who ended up dead.
Will I be your first?
Max, look out!
What the hell was that?
Did you see that?
Max?
You can't sleep, huh?
A nightmare.
Do you want some company?
No thanks. Vince, I want to be alone.
Please forgive me.
Vince?
Vince, is that you down there?
Your move.
Hey, who let you out?
Nobody
Where's Max?
He went to go talk with
someone called Jones.
Hm. I'm glad someone
up with these things.
Where's Roxanne?
Why?
Hey, listen. After that stunt you pull last night,
you should be laying down in the cell next to Sid.
You couldn't kill me.
You don't have it in you.
Wanna play?
Morning, honey.
How come she's not your girlfriend?
The way she acts around you..
.. seems like she likes you.
What the hell do you know?
Last night I could hear through
the walls. She was praying.
She was asking for God's forgiveness.
For a secret. A secret that
she's been keeping, even from Max
What secret?
"The gruesome discovery was made today
outside the tunnel of the plant remains.."
"The body of 17 years old girl was found in
an abandoned car in the local rock core."
"The authority was holding
a young man for questions."
Oh my God!
Vince, don't sneak up on me, OK?
Did you hear that?
No
It was nothing.
What's the matter, princess?
I think about Sidney.
I could've save him.
Wait. That wasn't your fault.
It's not your fault, baby.
Thanks, Vince.
Have you ever missed me?
No. Can I go?
Sometimes, I missed you.
You asshole.
You swore that you
wouldn't say anything.
Deal is a deal. OK?
But you have been keeping secrets.
Which secrets?
I know about our
baby. And what you did.
How? I never told anybody.
Then, why you shouldn't told me.?
Vince, it was a mistake.
It's OK. I just want
you one more time.
Rox. If Max knew what you did,
.. you think he will still
see you fit to be mother?
Our secret
Your call was a disaster
I know. It was a mess.
Damn kid are hands full.
I didn't ask you for report card.
- Yeah
Obviously we're not
arranging a withdraw today.
The reason I had to drive
5 hours to hear that?
Well, Max. If you are able to provide proof
of life we wouldn't have these problem.
See what's in front of you?
We are around the box.
The one inspired him, death
What this got to do with it?
It doesn't got anything to do with it.
You only got one choice now. Kill the kid.
You heard me. Grabbed
the kid, not kill him.
It was one bad call.
We'll call again.
Her mother would pay.
Any parent would pay.
We're not done until we
get the money. You got me?
No, you don't get me, Max.
You're gonna do what I tell you.
Be prepare to dispose the body.
You must be aware with
all the possibilities.
I'm not killing anyone.
And sure not an 8 year old.
Huh! If only you knew
who you are dealing with.
Listen, Jones. I don't give a
damn who you are. I ain't doing it.
The last thing I could cut off
his ear and send it to his mom..
Less effective than
what you might think.
Return the phone. We'll meet tomorrow morning
for the last time time. Your restaurant.
What's the deal, Jones?
- What?
Jones? I'm not Jones. I don't know
what are you talking about. I swear!
What the hell is this?
I'm not Jones, man. I
don't know any Jones.
Then who the hell called me?
Somebody said they pay me, OK? To leave the
phone and pick it up once it was put back
You got the pay check.
What he looked like?
What did you do?
Is that your remember?
Hey, kid.
- Abrakazzam
That's cute. Give it here.
I give to Max when I tell him.
Tell him what?
About you and Roxanne.
Oh. Check.
Do you like games,
huh? I know a game.
Come on. Down there.
David?
So where we going?
Play my game. OK? I'm
going to show you something.
Stop right there.
Do you see that? To the trees?
Just keep looking.
I don't like this game
Are you gonna cry?
Oh, I thought you might need that.
No.
Got some more to say? Huh?!
Please. Don't kill me
I told you. You still
don't have it in you.
David! Come back here!
David?
David!
Your move, Vince.
Very clever.
I'm just gonna wait right here.
Well, you see. The
longer you make me wait..
Are you done running?
Good. Very good.
Because I'm gonna break you legs.
David
You wanna yell out for Max?
Maybe he could help you.
But who's gonna help you?
Are you threatening me?
Jesús!
No. Not Jesús.
Checkmate
David!
He fell!
I got you.
Yeah?
It's Marla.
FDA licensing database got
a hit on Vincent Delayo.
Looks like he filled an order
for insulin two days ago.
I thought that might
just work. Where?
Regie's Pharmacy, 227 Maine Street,
Welsham, Maine. I'll call Whitney now.
Don't.
I'll tell him for you.
See you soon, kiddo.
Your eyelids look heavy.
Dreams. Bad dreams, David.
No more Vince though.
That was the most horrible thing.
Did it make you just
a little bit happy?
Happy?
You think what happened
to Vince made me happy?
I can see it in your eyes.
I heard that the eyes are
the window of the soul.
David!
Could you leave us a few minutes?
No problem, Max.
Sorry I was away.
Then don't go see Jones tomorrow.
I have to get our money.
No. Baby, everytime you
leave, something awful happens.
Look. Just let David go
tonight. Can we please..
Rox, we need the money.
That's what happens when everybody
wins. Your friends are dead.
I've no idea why we trap here.
And these things I hear in the middle of night. I wake
up and I hear like somebody putting ideas in my head
Hey. Hey, easy. Easy. Look
at me. We're almost there.
Where's your ring?
I'm cleaning it.
There's something
wrong about this place.
We leave tomorrow. I promise.
Looking for this?
It was your ring in Vince's bed, Rox.
No, Max. You don't
understand. I can explain.
He made me..
.. you do what?
Max, you were away for 3
years. And I had no one.
And I made a mistake. Vince's
gonna tell you but.. I had..
Max
Can I come, Max?
Where are you going, baby?
To the meet.
At 7 at night?
I'll be early.
You can't leave me alone!
Does Roxanne know that
you're going to kill me?
Stay right there, ma'am.
How many of you?
I asked you a question
I'm alone
Easy, ma'am.
You found me, Mr Policeman.
For a time, I don't
think that you would.
Everything is going
to be alright, David.
Our life are like stories, you know?
There will be beginning,
a middle and the end.
Max's story. Your stories
are here too, Mr Policeman.
Would you like to know how it ends?
Police Suspect Child Dead
Why haven't you told him about
the fallens in the basement?
Don't make things up.
There's nothing down there.
Believe if you will.
Not another step, lady.
Open the door
You're going for a long time.
Open the door, lady.
Better do something, Roxanne.
Can't have babies in prison.
This is your last
chance. Open the door.
Last chance!
Get away. I killed that man.
Roxanne, you had no choice.
I did't want him die.
Of course you didn't.
It's gone.
My whole life I had it.
What are you, David?
I'm an angel
The voices in your dreams.
What did they tell you?
They tell me to kill
Max but I would never-
Their souls, Roxanne,
is going to hell.
No, baby. Hell's not real.
It's something that the parents
frightened their children with. There's no-
such place.
Are you certain?
I've seen it, Roxanne.
The wicked, an eternal damnation
God will punish Max
for his wickedness.
Max isn't like that.
Not yet. But he means to kill me.
The murder of an angel
No, he would never.
Eternal damnation, Roxanne.
Please, David. I'll do anything.
Would you kill for him?
To save his soul?
Would you kill him for him?
While you decide, you help me with the
fire. I'm too young to play with matches.
Sam. Get away from there.
Our business is nearly concluded.
I know you're watching me.
I'm not playing this game anymore.
Good. This is a business to you. And you'll
aim your ammo bullet to the back of his head.
That's not the deal I made.
How dare you hang up on me? You
had a bad 4 days with David, Max?
Try 8 years?
You're Jones?
There's enough here for more than
just a down payment, don't you think?
I'm not gonna murder a little boy.
That is the last it is.
Do you really think he's human?
We have something in common you and I. We both let
the wolf in our home and lock the door behind it.
When I adopted him, I've got
the life I've always wanted.
But you've no idea
what he is capable of.
Or all the ways he can get to you.
I'll give up all I
have to get rid of him.
He just get inside your head and
he whispers these horrible thoughts,
and paints these
visions you can't escape.
He is getting stronger, Max.
And I have no idea what he could be
capable of in a year or a week or even now
and he is not gonna stop.
until all of us are dead.
Who's watching him over right now? He killed
his own father. He killed his last nanny.
Do you not think he's
going to kill her?
Listen to me. I am begging
you. Please. Kill him.
You had the wrong guy.
No, please.
I'm sorry.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
I'm sorry. You have
reached the number...
Shhh.. Do you hear it, Roxanne?
Hear what, baby?
Bad man coming.
Rox?
Rox!
What are you gonna do to, David?
Nothing.
Max, say you forgive me.
Of course I forgive you.
Hide, David!
Get the gun, Max.
Take the cop's gun.
Run.
Put the gun down, Rox.
We can get out of here and
leave all these behind us.
You.
David!
No!
Max!
For your soul, Max!
David, come to me!
Get out of here, Rox!
Over here.
Come and get me.
Look
Hey, Max.
Behind you.
Nice shot, Max.
Oh God, Rox.
You can't leave me.
Don't-
Rox, I'm sorry.
Rox!
Oh, no!
No, no, no.
I'm just getting started here.
Poor Roxanne. She
thought I was an angel.
You can't kill an angel.
Demon, maybe.
Ah... What's a demon?
One of the angel who fell.
Like you're gonna fall, Max.
Don't look so sad, killer.
You're on a winning team now.
No commandments. No guilt.
I was sent for those
that are desperate.
I come to them when they are weak.
When their lives are hopeless.
When those they love reject them.
I come to them. Whisper into their
ear and I can be very convincing.
Why, David?
Why all this?
Casting for souls, Max.
That's what I do.
And me?
What do I do?
You're as weak as the rest of them.
So be a good boy and
put the gun to your head.
Do it.
Or hear my voice every
moment for your life.
It was a good game, Max.
Good game, Max. But it's not over.
Yeah, David. It is.
Rox?
You can't kill an angel, Max.
They will always be with you, Max.
Always.
Ho! Ho! Ho!
Merry Christmas!
Bless you... Merry Christmas.
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com