www.titlovi.com
- Hello?
- It's me.
Oh, am I bothering you, Francesco?
No, don't worry, I had to get
out of the shower some time.
Hold on a minute, Franco...
You were saying, Franco?
No, no, nothing. Just
calling to see how you doing.
You know how things are...
...life goes on.
Gnaghi!
I've been shouting at
you for hours. Gnaghi!
He's Ghigini, the surveyor.
- 12th row, 3rd grave, right?
- Gna.
Grave three.
Here we go.
I know you've heard this before,
but this time,
my dear Ghigini,
it is forever.
Rest in peace!
Oh, my back...
What a waste of good marble.
Never looks right when you fix it.
All this fancy packaging.
I don' know why they don't
just cover the graves with dirt.
The gun! I forgot the fucking gun!
- Ea...t!
- Gnaghi,
give me the spade! Gnaghi!
give me the fucking spade!
There we go.
You handle the rest Gnaghi.
My name is Francesco Dellamorte.
Weird name, isn't it?
Francis Of Death.
Saint Francis Of Death.
I often thought of having it changed.
Andrea Dellamorte would
be nicer, for example.
I'm the watchman of
the Buffalora cemetery,
I don't know how the epidemic started,
All I know is that some people,
on the 7th night after their death
come back to life.
I call them "Returners",
but frankly I can't understand
why they're so anxious to return.
The only way to get rid
of them once and for all,
is to split their heads open.
A spade'll do it, but a
Dum-Dum bullet is best.
Come and have a glass of wine.
Is this the beginning of an invasion?
Does it happen in all cemeteries,
or is Buffalora just an exception?
Who knows? And in the end, who cares?
I'm just doing my job.
Good morning engineer.
How are you doing today?
Fine, Miss Chiaromondo. And you?
The cemetery is open, isn't it?
For you, any time.
Hello cutie. Here...
How are you?
He's happy. He likes
it when the sun shines.
I'm not an engineer...
...and you are no cutie.
Poor Gnaghi, on his ID card it reads:
"Distinctive physical marks: all".
He has a real passion for dead leaves,
can't stand it when the
wind blows them away...
Oh well,
we all do what we can
not to think about life.
The most beautiful living
woman I have ever seen!
Will I see her again?
I just came to water the flowers
on your poor father's grave.
Husband.
How long has he been dead?
Two weeks.
- Thank goodness.
- What?
- I mean, I'm very sorry.
- Have you no respect for pain?
Well, you know how these
things are... You see:
- in time, pain heals.
- It's not healing a bit.
He was wonderful,
he was a wonderful lover, incredible,
tireless.
He was fantastic!
I messed it all up,
I've lost her.
Will I see her again?
Hey, Franco!
Franco is the only living person
who even calls me. Now and
then I stop by his office
to remind myself what he looks like.
You can't live on memories alone.
It's for you. Sign as usual.
- Have you got a pen?
- No.
Hold on a sec, here we are.
Have you had any visits last nights?
A couple, yes.
All this extra work! It's
much if the pay me any more.
Tell the Mayor...
Oh, tell the Mayor then what?
They'd close the cemetery.
Good-bye job and
good-bye house!
Come on, who do you
think would believe you?
Listen, I don't care if
you don't believe me Franco,
you're not the one who pays me!
I believe you,
I believe you, and you're right...
- At least have him pay the overtime.
- Good.
Well, let's go to the Mayor, then!
It's not that easy.
First you have to fill out an M3 form,
report with an M3 form...
Forms...
I could speed things up there for you...
It's easier just to shoot them.
One M3 form!
Going to get our willies wet tonight?
Some of us, yeah.
Hell, at a certain point
in life, you realize
you know more dead people than living.
Sorry about the other day, I was
a bit crass. I didn't mean to be.
My name's Francesco Dellamorte.
You know, this is the
only job I could get
even with a degree in biology.
Anyway we all end up here
sooner or later, don't we?
I've got a great little
house... Want to see it?
I don't live alone, I've
got a helper, Gnaghi.
He's a real conversationist!
The cemetery's small, but
it's got a marvellous ossuary!
An ossuary...
I have never seen anything so...
exciting!
Neither have I.
It's like in my dreams!
This is my dream.
I couldn't ask for anything more.
Me neither.
You know, you've got
a real nice ossuary.
Thanks.
You will allow me to return, won't you?
You will allow me to kiss
you just once, won't you?
No.
Not like this.
Like this.
I must be faithful to
the memory of my husband!
I can't. I can't!
It's not my fault... It's this place.
I feel strange tremors.
It's not the cold...
I'm not afraid...
This place wants me to...
It's forcing me to...
I don't want to!
I can't! I can't!
Don't be afraid, it's just ignis fatuus.
Why here?
Why on your poor husband's grave?
I've never kept anything from him...
We trusted each other implicitly.
He would have liked to know.
Well, if that's the case...
All these lights!
Let them watch.
What's better than watching
two lovers making love, hey?
Just to have a bit of privacy.
Sorry, but the lady wants stars only.
It's never been like
this before, with anybody.
Only you.
No one will ever make us part.
Gnaghi! The gun!
I can explain! Listen to me,
you've always been so understanding!
That's life!
It's nothing my love,
you're fine.
Great,
just when I don't need it anymore.
Well don't just stand there!
Go call doctor Vercesi!
Go on, get the doctor!
Go on! Move!
Nothing can separate us.
I swear, nothing.
Nothing will separate us, will it?
Nothing, my love. Nothing.
Not even death?
Not even death.
Dellamorte, are you
in there? Dellamorte!
Jesus! You scared me to death!
Were you looking for
me, Chief Straniero?
Yes, Dr. Vercesi called.
What happened last night?
Well you know. Why are
you asking me? She's dead.
I know she's dead,
but how did that happen?
Her husband.
Sure! He came back from
the dead, he raped her,
then bit her to death.
Is that what he did?
No, he didn't rape her.
Oh, you always crack me up, you know!
Dr. Vercesi, are you spying on us?
No, I dropped this certificate.
Her heart stopped from fear, it
wasn't the bite that killed her.
She died while making...
well you know... doing it.
You know what that means, my boy?
I'll have to look somewhere else
for the creep who killed her!
- You are no longer a suspect.
- Why not?
Well, you know what I mean.
Look, don't make me say it!
Go on, you can say it. I
don't mind, I'm impotent!
Don't use that word! A young
man like you, at your age...
Did she have any relatives?
No, no relatives, no friends.
Well, I have to say that...
Shit! This is definitely not my style!
- Can I keep her here?
- If you pay for the funeral, of course
you can do whatever
the hell you want with her.
- Does that wrap it up, then?
- Yeah, except for a killer on the loose.
Care to join me for a cup of tea?
The weather's changing at last!
I can't forgive myself
for having lied to you:
I don't have a degree in biology,
I didn't even finish high school.
I haven't read more than
two books in my whole life:
one,
never finished,
and the other is the phone book.
I don't want her to become a Returner.
I don't want to see her again.
No!
Yes, my love!
No, don't make me do it!
But if you do it so well... so well!
Not to you!
It will be better with
me than with the others!
Gna!
You do it!
Well go on! If you finish
fast I'll buy you an ice-cream.
Gna!
- Here comes the Unforgiven.
- Who?
The Tombstone Mayor.
The man whose dick's so
small he pees with tweezers.
He could become a
woman. That'd solve it!
They are sewing them
back on in the States now.
Yeah, they can stitch it right on,
if you've got one to start with.
Forget it, I started that rumour.
The more they laugh, the
further away they seem.
You can never be too different, Gnaghi.
Maybe you can.
Engineer!
Engineer, engineer, come! Have a seat!
Well well well, what a surprise!
Yes! It's a miracle
seeing you here, engineer!
It's a miracle seeing
you here, Mr. Mayor.
So, how are things down at
our cemetery? How are things?
Well how do you think things are?
Population's shrinking.
You're lucky, my dear engineer!
You just can't imagine how
things are at the Town Hall.
Now that the elections are upon us,
it is chaos, right, inspector?
Yeah, it's a thrill for all,
nobody wants to lose their job.
I was hoping for a New Deal...
Daddy, what's this?
This is my assistant Gnaghi.
He's sweet!
Will you buy him, daddy?
That's great, it even knows how to cry!
Gnaghi, don't stay so close to her.
Could you move over, darling?
Would you tell your
daughter to move over please?
Yes of course.
Sometimes Gnaghi gets a little bit excited...
Oh, I'm sure he's
charming. Now, where was I?
What's he doing? Dancing?
No, no, he's just about to...
What the hell are you doing Valentina?
He threw up on me, Claudio!
Oh, a new fact!
Would you like to go for a ride?
I knew you'd understand!
Take off!
By the way, one of these days
I have to talk to you
about the cemetery.
The youth of today...
They're so... emotional.
Come on, Gnaghi! Get in, for God's sake!
Don't do this, just get in the car!
It's not the end of the world,
It didn't even bother her!
She understood it was just a
demonstration of your affection.
Anyway, it's not the first time
you threw up over a woman, is it?
Come on, Gnaghi, get in!
Look, first love doesn't count.
It's last love that counts!
Nobody came today.
I was a bit bored,
not even the admiral...
he's just disappeared!
Let's hope tomorrow, okay?
Yeah, come again and stay a while.
Oh, he was such a
distinguished man, the admiral!
Always used to bring me, always,
a touch of Sambuca.
Oh, come on Gnaghi!
You'll get over, you'll see!
Time passes,
nothing seems the same...
It just gets worse.
God, is it ever difficult
trying to make you feel better!
What were you doing with the Mayor's
daughter anyway? She's only a child!
Gna!
Oh yeah, that's not true,
you are not a child, Gnaghi.
You're a year older than I am. Anyway...
One day,
you'll settle down with some...
poor creature like yourself.
In the meanwhile, why do you care?
They all end up here
sooner or later, Gnaghi.
Often sooner than later.
Faster, open it up!
- If daddy could see us now!
- He'd kill me!
Claudio!
- Off we go!
- Go!
Go! Go!
Go!
- Hang on!
- Eat our dust!
Four motorcycles racing...
The Mayor's daughter is on one of them.
Her head was sliced right off.
They had to sew it back on the body.
The bikes crashed into
a bus loaded with scouts
on their way back from
a church-sponsored rally.
Slaughter of the innocents!
And they were all so young.
They felt their life was ahead of them,
but in fact they were already passing by.
Well, you've got your hands full!
Oh, more than you know!
Gnaghi, we're going to
need a lot of bullets.
# Never should have gone
out on the Boy Scout picnic,
# never should have, never
should have gone just then.
# Never should have gone
out on the Boy Scout picnic,
# Never should have, now
I'll never go again! #
Claudio! Take me with you!
Don't leave me all alone, Claudio!
Take me with you, my love!
Nasty tart!
My son wasn't with you!
He was promised to the Mayor's daughter!
- But he loved me!
- Liar!
He was mine, he loved me!
- Only me!
- Have you no respect for a mother's pain?
We're born to die,
born merely to die.
Do you remember?
Just yesterday,
she was alive, happy.
Do you remember?
Dear Gnaghi even threw up on her,
and she took it so well!
And now, she's gone...
and right on the eve of the elections!
I better get the pickaxe and shovel.
Pumpkin, how could you do this to me?
Is it true as they say, that the
dead come back to life here at night?
Tell me the truth!
Hey! Who told you that?
Is it true or not? Is it true or not?
What if it is?
I've got to see Claudio again!
I have to know whether
he loved me or her!
If I hear anything, I'll let you know.
No, wait...
Go away! I haven't got
time for the living!
Gnaghi?
Gnaghi!
Gnaghi, they came back
sooner than we thought!
Gnaghi wake up!
Gnaghi, watch out!
Gnaghi,
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to.
Well, that's it, time's up and
I want you upstairs and
ready in five minutes! Okay?
Oh no, what's she doing here?
Visiting hours are over!
No one is going to
take me away from him!
Quick, get the fuck over here! Quick!
No, Claudio!
Claudio, take me with
you! Don't leave me!
Stupid cow!
Come on!
Wait! Wait!
Claudio please, take me with you!
Tell me you only love me!
Please...
Claudio!
You only love me, right?
Damn! It always shoots to
the right when it's cold.
Gnaghi!
No, please don't! He's only eating me!
Move aside.
Mind your business! I shall
be eaten by whoever I please!
This is my business. They pay me for it.
The living dead
and the dying living are all the same.
Cut from the same cloth.
But disposing of dead
people is a public service,
whereas you're in all sorts of trouble
if you kill someone
while they're still alive.
Wait!
This way they'll be together forever.
I'm sentimental.
Patience, Gnaghi.
In love, it's the waiting
that's the best part.
You have to learn how to wait.
- What's your name again?
- Gna!
Gnaghi.
I'm Valentina.
Haven't I seen you before?
Oh yeah. Now I remember.
You threw up on me. How sweet!
But I like shy boys.
And you never say no to a kiss.
Take advantage.
I'm certainly in no position
to refuse. Besides,
I don't think I'd refuse anyway.
False alarm!
It was only a cat.
No use you trying
to help me, little thing!
If I can't do it, imagine you...
Putting this skull together,
is one of the most difficult
things in the world.
You know, you really are
disgusting when you eat, Gnaghi.
Gna!
Yes, you're right. I suppose it all does
get mixed up in the stomach, in the end.
What is it?
That wasn't a cat!
We can't! I'm alive,
and you are dead.
I'm not prejudiced, my love.
I killed her!
Gna!
I killed her.
The first time, when her husband
bit her, she wasn't really dead.
When she woke up, and I
shot her, she was alive.
I killed her.
I killed the only woman I ever loved.
I shot her with my eyes closed,
didn't aim for the head.
That's why she came back.
God, what an idiot!
Now, I'm infected too.
Will I be a Returner when I die?
Who knows if Gnaghi...
No, poor Gnaghi, he'd
never have the guts
to crush my skull with a shovel.
I'm not dead, you idiot!
A bite can't kill you!
Good morning, engineer!
Miss Chiaromondo, I'm not an engineer.
Are you, or are you not
the watchman of the cemetery?
Well, of course I am.
You are therefore an engineer. By the way,
which of these do you think
would be better on my tombstone?
Both.
I like the opinion of
a handsome young man.
Good-bye, engineer.
- Gna!
- Good morning, cutie.
But that's the phone book.
Are you crazy?
That is my favourite reading!
Gnaghi, just because
we've got the new ones
doesn't mean to say we have to throw the
old ones away. These books are classics!
Gnaghi!
Gna!
Stop killing the dead.
They're mine.
If you don't want the
dead coming back to life...
why don't you just kill the living,
shoot them in the head?
Are you listening to me?
- Hello?
- Greetings from the Tomb oft the Town Hall.
- Franco! How are you?
- Bored.
Am I disturbing you?
No, you never disturb me.
Just called to talk about the scandal.
- Gnaghi, the door!
- All that crap.
What did you say?
What the hell was that?
Nothing, I'm...
- ...just working.
- What?
You know, daily grind.
Nothing but the daily grind.
You're telling me! Sometimes,
I feel like shooting myself.
How's everything in your life?
How are dear Mara and Cinzia?
You know, sometimes I wonder
if they really exist, Franco.
I mean, you do have a wife
and a daughter, don't you?
I only ask 'cause... sometimes
I think you've made it all up.
Franco, you do make me laugh!
You'll get out one day.
Buffalora will be
nothing but a bad, bad memory.
Yeah, or maybe not, if
only I could get unstuck...
I feel like a fly on fly paper.
You'll see, Franco...
Mara is going to get tired of you,
and Cinzia will grow up to hate you.
Then you'll be free.
Free to see what the rest
of the world looks like.
What do you think the rest
of the world looks like?
- The rest of the world?
- Uh-uh.
Who knows if the rest of
the world even exists...
Look who it is!
Hey, Dellamorte, come here!
At times, I get ahead of my work.
Work!
Dellamorte!
Gnaghi!
Francesco Dellamorte?
Where were you between
11 and 12:30 last night?
In bed.
Any witnesses?
I was talking to my friend Franco
on the telephone and I fell asleep.
Why, what happened?
Some fucking maniac
killed 7 people in town.
More work.
Well, you got to go to jail,
unless you have an alibi!
Why me?
Because your car was seen driving
around the streets last night, that's why.
That's impossible, no one
can drive that wreck apart from me.
Actually, I don't think it was you.
I think it was your assistant.
Gnaghi can't even roller-skate!
Neither can I, so what?
I want to question him immediately.
God, the weather's gone bad.
Please,
let me talk to him first.
Just tell him to come
right out, will you?
Don't you ever clean that
place? Jesus Christ, it stinks!
# When all is sad, when you're
alone, it feels so bad.
# You wait again for love to start,
to feel the beating of the heart. #
Gnaghi!
Gnaghi, I had a terrible dream last night,
I dreamt I went to town
and killed 7 real people.
Hi, remember me?
Dellamorte, you've
got important visitors!
You'll understand, engineer, after this massacre,
the voters are furious with me.
They've been voting
for you for 15 years.
If I don't find this maniac, Straniero,
there won't be a sixteenth.
What's your daughter got to do with it?
Now that the whole town is in mourning,
I want to show them
that I'm grieving as well.
I'll have some pictures
taken of the body
and put a blow-up on
my election posters.
And underneath, something like:
"if you've had a death in the family,
vote for someone who suffers like you."
What do you think?
Well, you know, it's a thought!
Or: "Vote
for a man who has lost
all other happiness."
Ready to shoot?
So what do I do? Take
one from the neck down?
Engineer?
What's the meaning of this?
Daddy!
Daddykin!
Did you hear that?
I don't know. It depends...
Daddypie!
Daddypooh!
Valentina!
Pumpkin!
The plot thickens!
Pumpkin, where are you?
Where are you?
Your Daddy's here!
Stop blabbering and come on in!
Coming.
Here I am, little one.
Jesus, it stinks in here!
It's my fault, daddy!
Oh my God, Valentina!
What are you doing on TV?
I'm rotting fast, Daddy!
You, stuttering monster,
you're the one who hurt my little girl!
No, he loves me!
Step aside!
I command you, as your Mayor!
With your consent, I'd
like to marry Gnaghi.
- This horrible thing?
- Gna!
I'm not such a great
catch either, Daddy.
Not as long, dear, as I've
got a breath in my body!
Alright. We'll fix that right away!
Help me, engineer!
I'm not an engineer!
I'm sorry Gnaghi,
she really was beginning to...
go off a bit on that, wasn't she?
He's dead?
He's dead.
Who took a bite out of his neck?
Well, not me or Gnaghi,
Take a mould of our teeth.
You'll see they won't match.
And who did it?
Oh, relax Straniero. This won't be
your first unsolved case, will it?
Hold it!
Oh, come on, Gnaghi...
The world's full of girls like
that, and they've got bodies, too.
By the way,
do you know what my
mother's maiden name was?
You'd never believe it if I told you.
She was called Dellamore.
Dellamore.
That means "love"...
You're not the only person in the
world who's lost a lover, Gnaghi.
Get down!
What do you think? Get down from there!
Forget it, engineer!
Go home!
You're supposed to be
setting a good example,
now will you get back to
your coffin immediately!
You can't stop me,
you owe your job to me.
- Remember?
- Get down or I'll shoot.
You can't.
I'm the Mayor!
Ex!
- Mr. Dellamorte?
- What?
I'm Civardi, the new Mayor.
Why the barbed wire?
Do they climb in at night?
No, they climb out, sometimes.
Would you mind coming down?
You reported an epidemic
which affects the dead.
You claim they come to life
within seven days of burial.
- It says so, right here.
- An M3 report.
- Didn’t you fill it out?
- No.
Oh, splendid.
So you'll provide us with a denial.
Just sign here.
Franco must have sent it.
What a nice thought.
Nothing happened.
Nothing ever happens.
If the press got hold
of something like this,
not only would Buffalora
be a laughing stock,
but you'd lose your job.
My personal secretary.
- Mr. Dellamorte.
- A pleasure.
A real pleasure, Mr. Dellamorte.
Thank you.
You and I are going
to get along just fine.
Good-bye.
Your name!
I didn't get your name...
Will I see her again?
Hi!
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to frighten you, Miss.
I was expecting someone else.
Miss! Miss!
Ever since I got to Buffalora,
strange things have
been happening to me.
It's as if I've been here before.
And that grave...
And you, Mr. Dellamorte, it's as if
I've known you forever.
As if I've loved you forever!
You love me, too?
Why?
Who else is there?
I love you as well.
I love you.
I've heard what they
say about you in town.
Is it true that you don't...
I mean, that you can't...
No, you don't wanna
believe town gossip.
Because I can only love an impotent man.
Yeah, it's true. It's true.
I like men...
but their manhood terrifies me.
I can't stand the thought
of them having a...
I mean... you understand?
It's a sort of phobia I have.
I don't have one, I don't
have anything at all.
Will you marry me?
I'm getting married!
Gna!
I'm really getting married!
Don't pretend you
didn't hear everything.
Gna!
Yeah? Why not?
Go ahead, explain...
God gracious...
What are you saying?
You heard me!
My dear boy,
you must be very run down.
I'm going to give you some pills.
Dr Vercesi, I'm serious.
Look, I'm not going to be
intimidated in my own surgery.
That waiting room there
is full of people with good,
honest diseases.
I'll pay you...
Yes I know, but...
How can I? I mean,
everybody knows that...
you haven't got one.
I see. You have got one.
When would you like me
to relieve you of your...
- ...problem?
- Now.
What are you waiting
for? Get on with it!
Now what?
I told you I don't want an anaesthetic.
It's not an anaesthetic.
What is it, then?
One shot of this, it'll be
as if you've never had one.
It lasts for over a month.
Look... please don't
make me cut it away.
Today I'm just not up to it.
What are you doing, turning over?
I have to give you
the shot in the front.
Front where?
Hold still, I'll just make a puncture.
That fucking butcher
has given me some kind of infection.
Gnaghi!
I'm hovering between life and death.
Gna!
Yeah, you're right.
I suppose I'm used to this condition.
That's her. Don't let her
in. Tell her I'm not here.
I don't want her to see me like this.
- I must see Mr. Dellamorte.
- Gna!
Please, I've got to speak
to him, is he in there?
I'd give my life to be dead.
Gnaghi!
It doesn't hurt anymore.
I think I'm better.
Gna!
When did t happen?
She was our nicest client.
The best always die first.
Gna!
Where have you been?
I thought I'd go mad.
If you only knew what happened to me.
If you only knew what happened to me...
I must talk to you.
We'll always be together.
Yes, my love, yes.
I don't know how to say this, but
- the Mayor raped me.
- No!
Wait! I liked it.
Not the violence, no.
But after that, we did it again nicely,
so that I'd forgive him.
It was wonderful, do you understand?
That means I'm cured. I
don't have a phobia anymore.
I can't marry you, now.
I'm going to marry him.
That doesn't mean
anything though, I mean,
nothing's changed
between us, I still love you.
You know that.
I just love you in a different
way, but you're important to me.
He knows, I mean, about you and me.
He's a wonderful man,
he said he's happy we can be friends.
We can still see each other.
Nothing's changed.
Everything's just as it was.
Everything.
You look for Death in the clear night,
you tell her you still love her,
that you are her slave,
that she's still your queen.
Death, Death,
Death, the whore.
No, I'd only do it for the fear
and I'd come back
just to experience the same fear again.
To be afraid,
always to be afraid.
Hi!
Is that white VW outside yours?
We're on foot.
Could you give us a lift?
It's not very far.
Go on!
I'm Magda.
And this is Laura.
How far is it?
This is where we live,
with another girlfriend.
Do you want to come up for a drink?
Come on, you're not afraid
of two college girls, are you?
Make a wish. I grant wishes.
I want you to fall in love with me.
But I'm already in love with you.
Haven't you noticed?
It's cold in here.
If you'd like to wash,
there's a sink there.
I didn't mean your face, silly!
I don't know whether I can do it.
I've been taking some medication...
I don't think your
medication is working!
Do you love me?
Yes,
if you stay all night.
All my life, too.
- Come on!
- Let's rest a bit.
- Why?
- You've come three times already.
Twice. The third one was faked.
She's sleeping, she's
been studying all day.
she's got an exam tomorrow morning.
I just wanted to get some wine.
Sit down.
I'll get you some.
Did Laura tell you you can pay me?
Pay you?
School’s expensive, my friend.
I have to pay you?
We don't have a scholarship, you know.
Besides, it's only 100,000 lira.
She told me she loved me...
That's 150,000.
She wants me to stay the night.
200,000.
Is a cheque all right?
It's money, isn't it?
Hurry, darling.
I'm cold.
Come and warm me up.
I need your warmth.
Warm me up.
Coming, love.
Now you'll be warm forever.
This time I'm really through with love.
I bet you'd like to know where I was
between 1 and 3 last night, wouldn't you?
I know, I know.
Here we are. Have no fear,
I won't tell anybody about this cheque,
this is the reason I came here.
We're both worldly men, aren't we?
- But this could be proof against...
- Proof against whom?
We've already arrested
the guilty party.
After setting fire to the apartment,
he went home, killed
his wife and daughter,
then turned himself in. He's at
the hospital, the psychiatric ward.
Somebody's stolen my crimes!
Sir?
Excuse me, this section
is closed to the public.
I've come to see the killer.
But you can't go in
there. He's in a coma.
He drank a whole bottle of iodine.
I have to take his measurements.
Franco!
You looked a lot better the last
time we talked on the phone.
Thief!
You're a thief...
You may have killed your wife and
daughter, OK, I'll give you that,
but it was me who knocked
off the three girls.
What are you doing stealing my murders?
What kind of fucking
friend do you think you are?
Especially as you thought
you were doing me a favour.
Put that out immediately!
- Smoking is not allowed in here!
- Shut up!
He's in a coma. He doesn't even notice.
Shit.
What'd you say?
Everything's shit.
The only thing that's not shitty...
is sleep.
What are you doing on the floor, sister?
She's praying.
Friend of yours?
Look, he hasn't got any relatives
and the coma he's in is irreversible.
Give me a signature
- and I'll pull the plug now.
- Fuck off!
Here we go. Put it back in there.
I won't let you die
until you give me an explanation.
Why did you steal my murders?
Don't you think anything
I do counts? Huh?
Oh, my God! What happened?
They killed each other. It
was a settling of scores.
Don't you believe me?
- No!
- Tough.
So bad...
So,
is that all you have any need
to say to your only friend?
Who are you?
I don't know you.
I don't know who you are.
Go away.
Go away!
Dellamorte, wait.
For God's sake, wait! There's
another maniac on the loose.
He's on the 4th floor killing people.
He already shot three.
You got a gun!
That's good. Now you can defend yourself.
Hey, take my advice and get
the hell out of here quick!
Straniero!
It was me!
You and I are both the same.
We kill out of indifference,
out of love sometimes,
but never out of hate.
Now I don't know who's dead or alive.
I'm sick of killing.
So I'm leaving the game, brother.
Dellamorte Dellamore
bids you farewell
and is on his way.
Where to?
Better get out of here.
Even the statue's talking.
Where do you think you're going?
if you haven't yet
understood the difference
between life and me.
Gnaghi, you're not bringing that!
That coffin is not coming with us!
Yeah, I missed that one. Don't
worry, I'll get the next one.
Oh calm down. I know
every bump on this road.
There's one!
Look!
I'd never been this far.
We made it, Gnaghi!
Who could have imagined this?
Wider than all the streets
of Buffalora put together.
- It never seems to end!
- Gna!
Hang on, Gnaghi.
Past this tunnel is
the rest of the world.
What do you think the rest of
the world looks like, Gnaghi?
Can you imagine it?
You're right. It's beyond imagination.
I should have known it.
The rest of the world doesn't exist.
Gnaghi!
Gnaghi, you weren't
hit that hard. Come on.
Come on, I'll take you
to the car. Come on,
Come on! Why are you going on
like this? You've just got cut.
Come on man, get up,
I'll take you to the car!
Come on! Come on, get up!
What? What?
Gnaghi!
Don't leave me alone
now. Gnaghi! Gnaghi!
Oh God!
Death,
death, death comes sweeping down,
filthy death the leering clown,
death on wings, death by surprise,
veiling evil from worldly eyes,
death that's born
as life succumbs, while death and love
two kindred drums, beat the time
till Judgement Day,
an actor
in a Passion Play,
without beginning, without end,
evermore.
Amen.
You're my best friend.
I didn't even realise it.
Could you take me home?
Please.
Gna.
# subtitles by lyliakar #
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com